<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Conesa web page on David Conesa&#39;s Web page</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in David Conesa web page on David Conesa&#39;s Web page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Current Status  Director of the Master in Biostatistics, Universitat de València. Editor in Chief SORT (Statistics and Operations Research Transactions). Associate Editor TEST (International Journal of Statistics and Probability, sponsored by the Spanish Society of Statistics and Operations Research). Associate Editor RevStat-Statistical Journal.  Research Interests Someone told me that the best way to describe what I do is to say that I am a stochastic modeller. Although the frequentist way of applying Statistics is not discarded, the way I liked the most is the Bayesian approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/info/</guid>
      <description>Research Interests Alan Gelfand told me once that the best way to describe what we do is to say that we are stochastic modellers. That is what I try to do, to model complex real situations in the presence of uncertainty. To do so, the way I liked the most is the Bayesian approach. Being from Valencia, this can be considered as kind of natural.
In line with this, I have been involved in the analysis of waiting lists for transplants, efficiency of banks, early detection of epidemics, environmental performance, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> Email: david.v.conesa AT uv.es Phone: +34-963543791   Mailing Address  Departament of Statistics and Operations Research
C/ Doctor Moliner 50
46100 Burjassot (Valencia)
Spain
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
